http://www.clancylaw.com/privacy-policy

---
Privacy Policy
HomeAttorneys--Patrick M. KinnallyPatrick M. FlahertyPaul G. KrentzJoseph C. LoranGerald K. HodgeMark MasurStaffPractice Areas--Personal Injury & Wrongful Death--Auto AccidentsTruck AccidentsMedical MalpracticeConstruction AccidentsProduct LiabilityPremises AccidentsPlane / Train AccidentsNursing Home NegligenceSexual AbuseGeneral & Commercial Litigation--Contract Disputes / Injunction LitigationLocal GovernmentCorporate and Partnership MattersReal Estate LitigationEstate LitigationCivil Litigation AppealsWorkers' Compensation--Medical BenefitsTemporary DisabilityPermanent DisabilityImmigration & Citizenship--Family-Based ImmigrationEmployment-Based ImmigrationImmigrant and Non-Immigrant VisasDeportation and Removal IssuesBusiness Counseling--Business Formations and StartupsBusiness Acquisitions and SalesBusiness Succession PlanningGeneral Business Counseling and PlanningEstate Planning--Simple and Complex EstatesWillsTrustsGuardianshipsVerdictsNewsPublications--Spotlight on JusticeBlogResourcesContact UsEspanol--Áreas De Ejercicio--Lesión PersonalLitigio General y Litigios ComercialesCompensación Para el TrabajadorInmigración y CiudadanaAsesoria Comercial y Planificacin de Caudales HereditariosAbogados--Patrick M. KinnallyPatrick M. FlahertyPaul G. KrentzJoseph C. LoranGerald K. HodgeMark MasurRecomendadosRecursos
2114 Deerpath Road, Aurora, Illinois 60506
630-907-0909
HomeAttorneysPatrick M. KinnallyPatrick M. FlahertyPaul G. KrentzJoseph C. LoranGerald K. HodgeMark MasurChristopher J. WarmboldStaffPractice AreasPersonal Injury & Wrongful DeathAuto AccidentsTruck AccidentsMedical MalpracticeConstruction AccidentsProduct LiabilityPremises AccidentsPlane / Train AccidentsNursing Home NegligenceSexual AbuseGeneral & Commercial LitigationContract Disputes / Injunction LitigationLocal GovernmentCorporate and Partnership MattersReal Estate LitigationEstate LitigationCivil Litigation AppealsWorkers' CompensationMedical BenefitsTemporary DisabilityPermanent DisabilityImmigration & CitizenshipFamily-Based ImmigrationEmployment-Based ImmigrationImmigrant and Non-Immigrant VisasDeportation and Removal IssuesBusiness CounselingBusiness Formations and StartupsBusiness Acquisitions and SalesBusiness Succession PlanningGeneral Business Counseling and PlanningEstate PlanningSimple and Complex EstatesWillsTrustsGuardianshipsVerdictsNewsPublicationsSpotlight on JusticeBlogResourcesContact Us
EspanolÁreas De EjercicioLesión PersonalLitigio General y Litigios ComercialesCompensación Para el TrabajadorInmigración y CiudadanaAsesoria Comercial y Planificacin de Caudales HereditariosAbogadosPatrick M. KinnallyPatrick M. FlahertyPaul G. KrentzJoseph C. LoranGerald K. HodgeMark MasurRecomendadosRecursos
Recent Victory
In a highly contested liability case, Paul Krentz and Christopher Warmbold asked a Kane County jury to award $928,000.00 to their client, a 63 year old driver, accused of running a red light, who was seriously injured in a car crash at the intersection of Route 47 and Plank Road. After a couple hours of deliberation, the jury returned a $903,000.00 verdict in their client’s favor. Read more on the Victory here:
Going the Distance.
Privacy Policy
This statement applies to the online collection of personal information via websites operated by and applications offered by Kinnally Flaherty Krentz Loran Hodge & Masur P.C. Details of the Privacy Statement follow immediately below.
What personal information is collected and how is that information used?
We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user (such as when ordering a product, registering an account or signing up for a newsletter), from our Web server logs, and through cookies.
We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you.
We do not share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
How is my personal information protected?
We have implemented certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
However, please note that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country. Regardless of where these activities occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected consistent with the principles set forth under this Privacy Statement.
Who has access to the personal information?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other customer data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except our approved agents and contractors, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement.
We rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access.
We will not disclose any personal information or information about your usage of our websites to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law.
How may I correct, amend or delete my personal information, or update my preferences?
You may cancel your registration or update your preferences at any time simply by contacting us.
If you do not want to receive information about our products or services, please contact us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us at:
Kinnally Flaherty Krentz Loran Hodge & Masur P.C. Law Firm
2114 Deerpath Road,
Aurora, IL 60506
Phone: 630-907-0909
© 2020 Kinnally Flaherty Krentz Loran Hodge & Masur P.C.
2114 Deerpath Road, Aurora, IL 60506 630-907-0909
Privacy PolicyDisclaimerReferralsSitemap
From our law offices in Aurora, we serve clients throughout the state of Illinois including the communities of Elgin, St. Charles, Geneva, Batavia, Elburn, Yorkville, Oswego, Bristol, Big Rock, Wasco, Maple Park, Montgomery, Plano, Sycamore, DeKalb, Sugar Grove, Aurora, Naperville, Warrenville, Morris, Ottawa, Joliet, Chicago, Kane County, LaSalle County, Grundy County, Kendall County, DuPage County, Cook County, DeKalb County, McHenry County, Ogle County and Lee County.
Notice:
Undefined variable: body_class in /home/ocvhgcloud03/public_html/domain_kfkllaw.com/templates/kfkl/index.php on line 267
